[{"answer": "Yes, exactly.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "But they have been released, is that right?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, we should start by reminding people, look, there have been inconsistent preliminary tests, those field tests are typically inaccurate, which is why they sent it to the lab.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 41, "question": "How dangerous is this situation, how easy is it now to create a ricin scare?", "qSentId": 40}, {"answer": "The FBI is investigating it.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "Is the FBI investigating it now?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Worst-case scenario, it can be terribly deadly.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "How deadly could they be, potentially, in the wrong hands?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Unfortunately, it's easier than a lot of other potential bio agents.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "How easy is it for somebody, a regular Joe in the street, to sit down, get on the computer, go to his local store, and create deadly ricin?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "Well, there's no question.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 107, "question": "Because of this particular threat, apparently targeting politicians, mayors, because of their position on gun control, will the other thousand mayors who have been signing up to this, will they now have to be properly protected more than they are already?", "qSentId": 106}, {"answer": "Well, it just started raining here, Piers.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "Chad, what's the latest?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I believe it's getting more severe in both directions.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 146, "question": "Do you believe it's getting worse?", "qSentId": 145}, {"answer": "We have had these before.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Have we had these before in the last 30 years?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, fundamentally, it's the guy that say, yes, there are environmental problems and global warming is real.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 195, "question": "What is a skeptical environmentalist?", "qSentId": 194}, {"answer": "Fundamentally, yes, Bill.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "Is that accurate?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "Do you believe that global warming is a real and present situation?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Yes, and humans are responsible.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "If you look at the U.N. Climate Panel, they have done a lot of surveys on a lot of these different studies.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "And to you, Bjorn, believe that as a consequence of that, there could be any effect whatsoever on the power or the volume of tornadoes, hurricanes or big storms?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Well, I just wanted to protect my rights, my Second Amendment rights.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 307, "question": "Why would anybody do that?", "qSentId": 306}, {"answer": "Well, to me, what I worry about, Piers --", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Do you know how many?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "I'm sure the number is high.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "Ones that you could go and buy?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Have a guess.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 328, "question": "What is the number?", "qSentId": 327}, {"answer": "No, that was an NRA statement, by the way, and I never necessarily agreed with it.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Would you arm every school, every hospital, every church, every shopping mall, every person that works in those places?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Well, you say what's wrong with America, but your home country of England has basically banned handguns in the hands of law abiding citizens.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "When that happens seriously?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, if guns are the reason for Sandy Hook and all these problems, I think we should disarm Barack Obama's security force.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "How many of those -- how many of those school children would have been killed if Adam Lanza had a rope at Sandy Hook?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Well, I didn't say he should be impeached unless we prove that it went to him.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "But why do you believe that President Obama should be impeached over it?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "I think all politicians should be limited to two terms, one term in office and one term in prison.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Well, I don't worry about that.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Do you think of one actual fact she has come up with has turned out to be true?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Is that a charge with which you would find the country guilty?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "I was feeling suicidal.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "How old were you when that happened and what were you feeling?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "That's the amazing thing, is really kind of basic to our message.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "And Glenn, were you aware of any of this?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "You have very, very low lows, depression, it used to be called manic depression, which is more descriptive.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "For those who have no idea what a bipolar condition is, what is the simple, layman's way of describing it?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Those facts that there are so many people living with this that don't have a voice and I think it's important that they know that there's other people out there like them.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "What persuaded you?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "No, I haven't.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 518, "question": "Have you spoken to either of them about it?", "qSentId": 517}, {"answer": "Yes, it can be.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 529, "question": "And it can be a happy situation that you come through to?", "qSentId": 528}, {"answer": "Huge respect.", "docId": "130529pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "What was your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 537}]